# AWIN DANJUMA YARKS

09029909583



awinflex@gmail.com



Gwagwalada, Abuja.



## SUMMARY

Dedicated and detail Oriented Data Analyst a beginner with accumulated 1 year 7month experience. I can perform the following task unfailingly Data cleaning data mining data visualization data wrangling Model creation predicting and analytic ABC presentation for easy understanding

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Data Analyst

Gender:

Male

Resident

Gwagwalada, Abuja

• State of Origin:

Plateau Bokkos

Local Gov't Area:Nationality:

Nigerian

• Date of Birth:

25 Sept, 1998

Next of Kin:

Danjuma Yak Massamo

Next of Kin Phone No: 09055263578

# **EDUCATION**

#### University of Abuja

Bachelor's Degree in Mathematics 2016 – 2021

#### WAEC

Government secondary school kwali 2013 – 2016

#### primary education

Ecwa goodnews nursery primary school 2002 – 2010

#### SKILLS

- · Data wrangling
- · Data cleaning
- Data minning
- · Data statistical analysis
- · Data model creation
- · Data prediction
- Data visualization
- · Data presentaion
- · Data base management
- · SQL analysis

# TOOLS

- Python
- Excel
- SQL
- · Power bi
- Tableau
- · Gretl

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### IHVN specialist hospital gwagwalada branch.

Hospital/special treatment clinic | 2019 - 2020

- · Data entry and collection
- Data mining ,statistic,data visualization,data analysis
- Tools
- · power point and excel

#### National youth service

Nysc service | 2021 - 2022

- Migration of manual form A and B data collection form to online data collection base using Google survey form
- · Data collection using Google survey
- · Analyze and visualize data
- · Presentation of analyze data
- · working with a team

#### kaggle Remote

- · Project and predictive model competition
- · Supervised and unsupervised model usage

#### Award

- · Letter of recommendation by nassarawa state coordinator.
- · Letter of commedation by nassarawa state university.

#### **PROJECT**

Visit

https://github.com/Awinmipalan

For visualization visit https://www.novypro.com/profile\_projects/awindanjuma